const qBank = [
  {
    question: 'Who said "Laugh it up fuzzball"?',
    answers: ["Darth Vader", "Princess Leia", "Han Solo", "R2-D2"],
    correct: "Han Solo",
    questionId: "001"
  },
  {
    question: "Who fired the shot that destroyed the Death Star?",
    answers: ["Han Solo", "Red #5", "Luke", "Chewbacca"],
    correct: "Luke",
    questionId: "002"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was Star Wars (episode IV: A New Hope) released?",
    answers: ["1981", "1947", "1977", "1979"],
    correct: "1977",
    questionId: "003"
  },
  {
    question: "Princess Leia is princess of which planet? ",
    answers: ["Alderaan", "Yavin", "Endor", "Dagobah"],
    correct: "Alderaan",
    questionId: "004"
  },
  {
    question: "What species is Chewbacca?",
    answers: ["Wookie", "Ewok", "Bantha", "Hut"],
    correct: "Wookie",
    questionId: "005"
  },
  {
    question: "How many parsecs did the Millenium Falcon take for the Kessel Run?",
    answers: ["14", "12", "4", "9"],
    correct: "12",
    questionId: "006"
  },
  {
    question: "Who created the Star Wars film series?",
    answers: ["George Lucas", "Steven Speilberg", "JK Rowling", "James Cameron"],
    correct: "George Lucas",
    questionId: "007"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the birth name of Darth Vader?",
    answers: ["Obi Wan", "Aragorn", "Anakin", "Luke"],
    correct: "Jabba-the-hut",
    questionId: "008"
  },
  {
    question: "AT-AT (All Terrain Armored Transport) Walkers make their first appearance in which Star Wars film?",
    answers: ["Attack of the Clones", "Last Jedi", "Empire Strikes Back", "Return of the Jedi"],
    correct: "Empire Strikes Back",
    questionId: "009"
  },
  {
    question: "How is the shape shifting Clawdite Zam Wesell killed?",
    answers: ["Stabbed", "Lightsaber", "Emperor Palpatine", "Toxic Dart"],
    correct: "Toxic Dart",
    questionId: "010"
  },
  {
    question: "Where was Jar Jar Binks from?",
    answers: ["Degobah", "Naboo", "Yavin", "Coruscant"],
    correct: "Naboo",
    questionId: "011"
  },
  {
    question: "What color is Yoda's lightsaber?",
    answers: ["Purple", "Blue", "Green", "Yellow"],
    correct: "Green",
    questionId: "012"
  },
  {
    question: "How many years does Force Awaken take place after Return fo the Jedi?",
    answers: ["3", "25", "30", "18"],
    correct: "30",
    questionId: "013"
  },
  {
    question: "What's the icy planet's name in Empire Strikes Back?",
    answers: ["Endor", "Hoth", "Tattooine", "Toth"],
    correct: "Hoth",
    questionId: "014"
  },
  {
    question: "How many languages does C3PO speak?",
    answers: ["Three", "Over 20 thousand", "Over 6 million", "Over 100"],
    correct: "Over 6 million",
    questionId: "015"
  },
  {
    question: "How many players in the Cantina Band?",
    answers: ["four", "seven", "ten", "three"],
    correct: "seven",
    questionId: "016"
  },
  {
    question: "Which large, slug-like creature is the most powerful crime boss on Tatooine?",
    answers: ["Boba Fett", "Chewbacca", "Jabba-the-hut", "Sebulba"],
    correct: "Jabba-the-hut",
    questionId: "017"
  },
  {
    question: "Which number order brought about the destruction of the Jedi Kinights?",
    answers: ["66", "99", "4.99", "1"],
    correct: "66",
    questionId: "018"
  },
  {
    question: "Who did Qui-Gon and Obi-Wan duel with?",
    answers: ["Emperor Palpatine", "Darth Maul", "Count Dooku", "Sebulba"],
    correct: "Jabba-the-hut",
    questionId: "019"
  },
  {
    question: "Which supreme leader commands the First Order?",
    answers: ["Emperor Palpatine", "Snoke", "Kylo-Ren", "Smaug"],
    correct: "Snoke",
    questionId: "020"
  },

  // do these

  {
    question: "What's the name of Han Solo's ship?",
    answers: ["Slave I", "Millenium Eagle", "Executor", "Millenium Falcon"],
    correct: "Millenium Falcon",
    questionId: "021"
  },
  {
    question: "What planet are Wookies from?",
    answers: ["Yavin", "Kashyyyk", "Tattoine", "Endor"],
    correct: "Kashyyyk",
    questionId: "022"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Luke and Leia's mother?",
    answers: ["Padme Amidala", "Queen Latifa", "Ashoka", "Mon Mothma"],
    correct: "Padme Amidala",
    questionId: "023"
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of species is Sebulba?",
    answers: ["Wookie", "Gun-gun", "Hut", "Snake"],
    correct: "Gun-gun",
    questionId: "024"
  }, {
    question: "What invisible power binds the galaxy together?",
    answers: ["The Force", "Light saber", "Atoms", "The Tokens"],
    correct: "The Force",
    questionId: "025"
  }, {
    question: "Where does Yoda go to live after the Jedi purge?",
    answers: ["Yavin", "Endor", "Tatooine", "Dagobah"],
    correct: "Dagobah",
    questionId: "026"
  },
  {
    question: "Anakin chops who's head off?",
    answers: ["Jango Fett", "Snoke", "Count Dooku", "Yoda"],
    correct: "Count Dooku",
    questionId: "027"
  }, {
    question: "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber?",
    answers: ["Purple", "Red", "Green", "Blue"],
    correct: "Pruple",
    questionId: "028"
  }, {
    question: "Which planet is covered in water, and where the clones were made?",
    answers: ["Coruscant", "Tatooine", "Kamino", "Kashyyyk"],
    correct: "Kamino",
    questionId: "029"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Jango Fett's son?",
    answers: ["Boba", "Snoke", "Kylo-Ren", "Anakin"],
    correct: "Boba",
    questionId: "030"
  }, {
    question: "Who is also known as Emperor Palpatine?",
    answers: ["Darth Sidious", "Snoke", "Darth Vader", "Count Dooku"],
    correct: "Darth Sidious",
    questionId: "031"
  }, 
  {
    question: "How did Obi-Wan kill Greivious?",
    answers: ["Light saber", "Knife", "Laser Blaster", "Fire"],
    correct: "Laster Blaster",
    questionId: "032"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Darth Vader's Star Destroyer?",
    answers: ["Death Star", "Executor", "Lasankya", "Millenium Falcon"],
    correct: "Executor",
    questionId: "033"
  }, {
    question: "Uncle ____ and Aunt ____ raised Luke.",
    answers: ["Qui-Gon, Amidala", "Owen, Beru", "Vader, Leia", "Greivous, Beru"],
    correct: "Owen, Beru",
    questionId: "034"
  }, {
    question: "who said 'it's a trap'?",
    answers: ["Ackbar", "Lando", "Obi Wan", "Anakin"],
    correct: "Ackbar",
    questionId: "035"
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle did Rey live in?",
    answers: ["AT-ST", "Star Destroyer", "AT-AT", "Millenium Falcon"],
    correct: "AT-AT",
    questionId: "036"
  }, 
  {
    question: "How many Sith are always there?",
    answers: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
    correct: "Two",
    questionId: "037"
  }, 
  {
    question: "Who killed Jabba the Hut?",
    answers: ["Leia", "Luke", "Han", "Jar-Jar"],
    correct: "Leia",
    questionId: "038"
  },
  {
    question: "What did Luke lose during his fight with Vader?",
    answers: ["His heart", "Leg", "Hand", "Hair"],
    correct: "Hand",
    questionId: "039"
  }, {
    question: "Where did the Clone Wars begin?",
    answers: ["Tatooine", "Geonosis", "Naboo", "Jakku"],
    correct: "Geonosis",
    questionId: "040"
  },
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
